A Guide to the Papers of Harry Walter Roberts 1921,1970
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Photographs
  - Family, Personal, Business
    - Association of Social Science Teachers 1954 (Box-folder 56:5)
    - Association of Social Science Teachers 1955 (Box-folder 56:6)
    - Association of Social Science Teachers 1956 (Box-folder 56:7)
    - Association of Socil Science Teachers 1960 (Box-folder 56:8)
    - Bears Killed in Dismal Swamp December 8, 1964 (Box-folder 56:9)
    - Conference 1950 (Box-folder 56:10)
    - Conference (Box-folder 56:11)
    - Conference (Box-folder 56:12)
    - Cooper and Baker/Faulty (VSU) (Box-folder 56:13)
    - Education Committee Award (Box-folder 56:14)
    - Family (Box-folder 56:15)
    - Family (Box-folder 56:16)
    - Family: Waring Oil Service (Box-folder 56:17)
    - Gandys, The (Box-folder 56:18)
    - The Grand Boule' 1946 (Box-folder 56:19)
    - Morgan at State 1937 (Box-folder 56:20)
    - Nu Lambda Chapter 1940 (Box-folder 56:21)
    - Rural Research (Box-folder 56:22)
    - Roberts Concret Block Co. (Box-folder 56:23)
    - Scenes, Central or South America (Box-folder 56:24)
    - Scenes, Central or South America (Box-folder 56:25)
    - Schools in Spotsylvania Co. 1941 (Box-folder 56:26)
    - Southeastern Council of Family, Relations Meeting 1964 (Box-folder 56:27)
    - Special Project Honoring Leslie Andrews 1956 (Box-folder 56:28)
    - Summer School for Ministers 1953 (Box-folder 56:29)
    - Summer Session at VIP 1951 (Box-folder 56:30)
    - Travels (Box-folder 56:31)
    - Vacation, San Sucs (Box-folder 56:32)
    - Virginia State 1930's (Box-folder 56:33)
    - World Government Conference 1951 (Box-folder 56:34)
    - Yale University Graduation (Box-folder 56:35)
  - Jerome Davis, Photographs
    - Adjutant to the General (Box-folder 57:1)
    - The Army Committee at the Front (Box-folder 57:2)
    - Begging at the Church (Box-folder 57:3)
    - The Bell in the Kremlin (Box-folder 57:4)
    - The Billets of Wood (Box-folder 57:5)
    - Better Class Russian Home Sunday, February 1920 (Box-folder 57:6)
    - The Canon in the Kremlin (Box-folder 57:7)
    - Three Children who sleep in the same room (Box-folder 57:8)
    - Community Delegates mingling with the crowd (Box-folder 57:9)
    - The courtyard of a tenement (Box-folder 57:10)
    - Day and Night Bed (Box-folder 57:11)
    - Dining Room of the Kropatun Palace (Box-folder 57:12)
    - Dr. Gunfill in a kyack (Box-folder 57:13)
    - Eating Breakfast (Box-folder 57:14)
    - Feeding the dogs (Box-folder 57:15)
    - Fishing Schooner/Schooner Sailing home (Box-folder 57:16)
    - Georgiana Davis and Mother February 1, 1916 (Box-folder 57:16)
    - Greek Orthodox Church of Olyphant, PA (Box-folder 57:18)
    - The Henry Ford Trade School (Box-folder 57:20)
    - In The Factory (Box-folder 57:21)
    - Irrigation Ditch being completed-Turkestan (Box-folder 57:22)
    - Junior Play Cast (Box-folder 57:23)
    - The Library of the Henry Ford Trade School (Box-folder 57:24)
    - The mode of travel (Box-folder 57:25)
    - Negatives-Transportation (Box-folder 57:26)
    - Negatives-Transportation (Box-folder 57:27)
    - Negatives-Group Scene (Box-folder 57:28)
    - One Family (Box-folder 57:29)
    - Parade of Russian Workers July 4, 1918 (Box-folder 57:30)
    - Pittsburgh (Box-folder 57:31)
    - Poster December 31, 1919 (Box-folder 57:33)
    - Raid on a Russian Club (Box-folder 57:34)
    - In a Kayak (Box-folder 57:35)
    - Room with Kitchen Sink (Box-folder 57:36)
    - Rudzatale, Peoples Commissar of Transportation (Box-folder 57:37)
    - Russian Home in North Dakota (Box-folder 57:38)
    - The Russian Village (Box-folder 57:39)
    - Peasant girls in Moscow (Box-folder 57:40)
    - Russian Soldiers July 1919 (Box-folder 57:41)
    - Russian Soldiers (Box-folder 57:42)
    - Member's of the Soviet (Box-folder 57:43)
    - Russian boys mining coal (Box-folder 57:44)
    - Russian home card party (Box-folder 57:45)
    - Russian wife in peasent dress (Box-folder 57:46)
    - Spruce Alley steel plant (Box-folder 57:47)
    - Students at work (Box-folder 57:47)
    - The tenements of Spruce Alley (Box-folder 57:49)
    - Their only snow slide (Box-folder 57:50)
    - Two tenements of Spruce Alley (Box-folder 57:51)
    - Ukranian Village-Drieprostray (Box-folder 57:52)
    - Unidentified Male (Box-folder 57:53)
    - Unidentified Female (Box-folder 57:54)
    - Unidentified Female (Box-folder 57:55)
    - Unidentified Female (Box-folder 57:56)
    - Unidentified Family (Box-folder 57:57)
    - Union of Russian Citizens (Box-folder 57:58)
    - Volkhov hydro-electric station (Box-folder 57:59)
    - Workers two and three family homes (Box-folder 57:60)
    - Y.M.C.A. Club May 1918 (Box-folder 57:61)
    - Pioneer Camp, Moscow (Box-folder 67:62)
    - Painting (Box-folder 57:63)
    - Street Sweeper, Moscow (Box-folder 57:64)
    - Union, Russia (Box-folder 57:65)
- Printed
  - African American Newspapers
    - The Tribune: Roanoke, Virginia Volume 10, No. 29 (O.S.) August 18, 1951 (Box-folder 85:1)
    - The Tribune: Roanoke, Virginia Volume 10, no.43 (O.S.) November 24, 1951 (Box-folder 58:2)
    - The Charlottesville Tribune Volume unknown No.49 July 14, 1951 (Box-folder 58:3)
    - The Circuit Volume 11, No. 12 November 2, 1950 (Box-folder 58:4)
    - The Circuit Volume 12, No. 4 February 1, 1951 (Box-folder 58:5)
  - The Expected
    - The Expected Volume 13 No. 10 October 1943 (Box 59)
    - T he Expected Volume 14 No. 4 April 1944 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 14 No. 9 September 1944 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 14 No.11 Novmeber 1944 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 14 No. 12 December 1944 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 15 No. 1 January 1945 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 15 No. 2 February 1945 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 15 No. 3 March 1945 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 15 No. 5 May 1945 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 15 No. 6 June 1945 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 15 No. 7 July 1945 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 15 No. 8 August 1945 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 15 No. 9 September 1945 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 15 No. 10 October 1945 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 15 No. 11 November 1945 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 15 No. 12 December 1945 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 16 No. 2 February 1946 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 16 No. 3 March 1946 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 16 No. 4 April 1946 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 16 No. 5 May 1946 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 16 No. 6 June 1946 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 29 No. 8 August 1957 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 30 No. 12 December 1958 (Box 59)
    - The Expected Volume 31 No. 12 December 1959 (Box 59)
  - The Zion Herald News
    - The Zion Herald News 1970, 1979, 1989 (Box-folder 59:1)
  - The Baptist Trumpet
    - The Baptist Trumpet June, December 1949 (Box-folder 59:2)
  - The Mountain Voice
    - The Mountain Voice 1948-1951 (Box-folder 59:3)
  - Religion and Labor
    - Religion and Labor 1957-1958 (Box-folder 59:4)
    - Religion and Labor 1959 (Box-folder 59:5)
    - Religion and Labor 1960 (Box-folder 59:6)
  - The Richmond Unitarian
    - Richmond Unitarian December 29, 1965 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian January 4, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian January 5, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian January 12, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian January 19, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian January 26, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian February 9, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian February 16, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian February 23, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian March 16, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian April 6, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian April 20, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian May 4, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian September 7, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian September 14, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian September 21, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian September 28, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian October 5, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian October 12, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian October 19, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian October 26, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian November 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian November 7, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian December 14, 1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian December 21,1966 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian January 11, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian January 18, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian January 25, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian February 1, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian February 8, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian February 15, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian February 22, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian March 1, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian March 8, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian March 15, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian March 29, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian April 5, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian April 12, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian April 19, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian April 26, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian May 3, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian May 10, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian May 24, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian June 7, 1967 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian March 23, 1968 (Box 60)
    - Richmond Unitarian (Box 60)
  - Newsletters
    - Virginia Council News Volume 2 No. 2 April 1946 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 3 No. 1 March 1947 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 3 No. 2 May 1947 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 6 No. 3 July 1, 1950 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 7 No. 1 January 1, 1951 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 7 No. 2 April 1, 1951 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 7 No. 3 July 1, 1951 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 7 No. 3 October 1, 1951 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 8 No. 1 January 1, 1952 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 9 No. 1 January 1, 1953 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 9 No. 2 April 1, 1953 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 9 No. 3 October 1, 1953 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 10 No. 2 April 1, 1954 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 10 No. 3 July 1, 1954 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Virginia Council News Volume 10 No. 4 October 1, 1954 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 11 No. 2 April 1, 1955 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 11 No. 3 July 1, 1955 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 11 No. 3 October 1, 1955 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 12 No. 1 January 1, 1956 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 12 No. 2 April 1, 1956 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 12 No. 3 July 1, 1956 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 12 No. 4 October 1, 1956 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 13 No. 1 January 1, 1957 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 13 No. 2 April 1, 1957 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 13 No. 3 July 1, 1957 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 13 No. 3 October 1, 1957 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 14 No. 1 February 15, 1958 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 19 No. 2 May 15, 1958 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 14 No. 3 August 15, 1958 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 14 No. 4 Novmeber 15, 1958 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 15 No. 1 November 15, 1959 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 14 No. 2 May 15, 1959 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 15 No. 3 August 15, 1959 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 15 No. 4 November 15, 1959 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 16 No. 1 March 15, 1960 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 16 No. 3 September 15, 1960 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 16 No. 4 December 15, 1960 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 17 No. 1 March 15, 1961 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 17 No. 3 September 15, 1961 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 18 No. 1 March 15, 1962 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 18 No. 2 June 15, 1962 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 18 No. 4 December 1962 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News (2) Volume 19 No. 1 March 1963 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 19 No. 2 June 1963 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 22 No. 1 March 1966 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 22 No. 2 June 1966 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 22 No. 13 September 1966 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 22 No. 4 December 1966 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council News Volume 23 No. 1 March 1967 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Annual Report January 24-25, 1956 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Yearbook 1953 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Yearbook 1954 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Yearbook 1955 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Yearbook 1956 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Yearbook 1959 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Yearbook 1960 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Yearbook 1961 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Yearbook 1962 (Box 60)
    - Virginia Council of Churches-Yearbook 1964 (Box 60)
    - The NAACP Bulletin Volume 1 No. 2 January 1941 (Box 61)
    - The NAACP Bulletin Volume 1 No. 3 February 1941 (Box 61)
    - The NAACP Bulletin Volume 1 No. 7 June 1941 (Box 61)
    - The NAACP Bulletin Volume 1 No. 8 July 1941 (Box 61)
    - The NAACP Bulletin Volume 1 No. 9 August-September 1941 (Box 61)
    - The NAACP Bulletin Volume 1 No. 10 October 1941 (Box 61)
    - The NAACP Bulletin Volume 1 No. 11 Novmeber 1941 (Box 61)
    - The NAACP Bulletin Volume 1 No. 12 December 1941 (Box 61)
    - The NAACP Bulletin Volume 2 No. 2 Feberuary 1942 (Box 61)
    - The NAACP Bulletin Volume 21 No. 3 March 1942 (Box 61)
    - The NAACP Bulletin Volume 2 No. 4 April 1942 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 4 No. 1 January 1943 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 5 No. 9 September 1944 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 5 No. 10 October 1944 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 5 No. 11 November 1944 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 6 No. 2 February 1945 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 6 No. 3 March 1945 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 6 No. 4 April 1945 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 6 No. 5 May 1945 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 6 No. 6 June 1945 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 6 No. 7 July 1945 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 6 No. 8 August 1945 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 6 No. 9 September 1945 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 6 No. 10 October 1945 (Box 61)
    - The Southern Frontier Volume 6 No. 11 November 1945
    - The NAACP Bulletin (Box-folder 61:1)
    - The Southern Frontier (Box-folder 61:2)
    - Journal-Race Relations October, November, December 1944 (Box-folder 61:3)
    - Journal-Race Relations January, February, March 1945 (Box-folder 61:4)
    - Journal-Race Relations April, May, July 1945 (Box-folder 61:5)
    - Newsletter-The Southern Patriot 1955, 1965 (Box-folder 61:6)
    - Printed-Wilberforce 1956-1957 (Box-folder 61-7)
    - Newsletters-Wilberforce 1959-1960 (Box-folder 60:8)
    - The Voter Education Project 1964 (Box-folder 61:9)
    - Va. C.H.R- Newsletters 1958-1959 (Box-folder 61:10)
    - Va. C.H.R. Newsletters 1960 (Box-folder 61:11)
    - Va. C.H.R. Newsletter (Box-folder 61:12)
    - YMCA (Box-folder 61:13)
  - Printed Programs and Brochures
    - Announcements (Box-folder 62:1)
    - Brochures (Box-folder 62:2)
    - Bulletins-Agriculture (Box-folder 62:3)
    - Citizen Committee-The Case of William Schneiderman (Box-folder 62:4)
    - Conference on Adult Education 1956-1957 (Box-folder 62:5)
    - Flyers (Box-folder 62:6)
    - MAWM Flyers 1942 (Box-folder 62:7)
    - Printed Bulletin (Box-folder 62:8)
    - The Nansemond Story (Box-folder 62:9)
    - Journal-National Negro Health News 1937-1938 (Box-folder 62:10)
    - Obituaries (Box-folder 62:11)
    - Programs (Box-folder 62:12)
    - Programs (Box-folder 62:13)
    - Programs (Box-folder 62:14)
    - Program-Rural Church Institute Maryland 1947 (Box-folder 62:15)
    - The Origin of Race (Box-folder 62:16)
    - Sixth Mount Zion Baptist Church (Box-folder 62:17)
    - The Virginia Students Civil Rights Committee 1965 (Box-folder 62:18)
    - The Virginia Negro Baptist Home (Box-folder 62:19)
  - Journals and Pamphlets
    - Annual Report of the Lott Carey Baptist Foreign Mission Society of the U.S.A 1925-1926 (Box 63)
    - Negro Women in Industry in 15 States 1929 (Box 63)
    - U.S. Dept of the Interior Office of Ed. Bulletin No.8 1933 (Box 63)
    - U.S. Dept of the Interior Office of Ed. Bulletin No.10 1933 (Box 63)
    - U.S. Dept of the Interior Office of Ed. Bulletin No.12 1935 (Box 63)
    - U.S. Dept of the Interior Office of Ed. Bulletin No.13 1935 (Box 63)
    - The Quest for Understanding 1935 (Box 63)
    - Women At Work-U.S. Dept of Labor-Women's Bureau 1934 (Box 63)
    - Women At Work-U.S. Dept of Labor-Women's Bureau 1939 (Box 63)
    - U.S. Office of Education-Negro High School Graduates and Non-Graduates 1940 (Box 63)
    - Negro Women War Workers - Women's Bureau 1945 (Box 63)
    - Report of the Virginia Advisory Legislative Council 1945 (Box 63)
    - That You May Know-The Richmond Urban League Annual Report 1947 (Box 63)
    - Negro Women and their jobs-U.S. Dept of Labor-Women's Bureau 1954 (Box 63)
    - Race in the News 1950 (Box 63)
    - America, The South and Desegregation 1956 (Box 63)
    - SCAUL Newsletter 1 1965 (Box 63)
    - SCAUL Newsletter 2 1965 (Box 63)
    - SCAUL Newsletter 3 1965 (Box 63)
    - The Journal of Social Science Teachers April 1951 (Box 63)
    - The Journal of Social Science Teachers May 1, 1957 (Box 63)
    - The Journal of Social Science Teachers (3) August 1959 (Box 63)
    - The Journal of Social Teachers November 1960 (Box 63)
    - The 37th Annual meeting of the VA. Social Science Assn. April 15, 1964 (Box 63)
    - The 38th Annual meeting of the VA. Social Science Assn. April 24, 1965 (Box 63)
    - The 39th Annual meeting of the VA. Social Science Assn. April 19, 1966 (Box 63)
    - The 33th Annual meeting of the Association of Social Science Teachers (3) April 1968 (Box 63)
    - Democracy for Dixie (3) June 1941 (Box 63)
  - Postcards and Scrapbooks
    - Scrapbook-American council Report on Race Relations (Box 64)
    - Postcards-Printed (Box 64)
    - Printed-The PWA School Building-Aid Programs and Separate Negro Schools (Box 64)
    - Scrapbook- The Churchman 1955-1967 (Box 64)
    - Printed- Africa Report October 1963 (Box 64)
    - Printed- South African Scope September 1961 (Box 64)
    - Printed- South African Scope February 1962 (Box 64)
    - Printed- Interracial News Service July-August 1951 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 8 No. 9 September 1956 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 9 No. 1 and 2 January-February 1957 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 9 No. 3 and 4 March-April 1957 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 9 No. 5 and 6 May-June 1957 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 9 No. 7 and 8 July-August 1957 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 10 No. 1 and 2 January-February 1958 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 10 No. 3 and 4 April 1958 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 10 No. 6 June 1958 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 10 No. 7 July 1958 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 10 No. 10 October 1958 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 10 No. 11 November 1958 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 10 No. 12 December 1958 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 11 No. 1 January 1959 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 11 No. 2 February 1959 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 11 No. 5 May 1959 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 11 No. 6 June 1959 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 11 No. 7 July 1959 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 11 No. 8 August 1959 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 11 No. 9 September 1959 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 11 No. 10 October 1959 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 11 No. 12 December 1959 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 12 No. 1 January 1960 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 12 No. 3 March 1960 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 12 No. 4 April 1960 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 12 No. 5 May 1960 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 12 No. 6 June 1960 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 12 No. 7 July 1960 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 12 No. 8 August 1960 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 12 No. 9 September 1960 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations News Volume 12 No. 12 December 1960 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations Journal Volume 14 No. 1 and 2 January-June 1957 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations Journal Volume 14 No. 3 and 4 July-December 1957 (Box 64)
    - Race Relations Journal Volume 15 No. 1 and 2 January-June 1958 (Box 64)
    - Program-Institute of Race Relations and Clinic in Human Relations March 12-16, 1945 (Box 64)
    - Printed-South Afrcian Institute of Race Relations 28th annual Report 1956-1957 (Box 64)
    - Printed-South African Institute of Race Relations 30th annual Report 1958-1959 (Box 64)